<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Ace, by DAISY</title>
    <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Ace, by DAISY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Command line interface</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/cli/</guid>
      <description>Overview The easiest way to run Ace is to type this on the command line:
$ ace ~/Documents/book.epub  You&amp;rsquo;ll then see a decription of Ace&amp;rsquo;s actions as it runs tests on the book. The JSON report is printed to the command line at the end (nothing is saved to disk; you need to specify --outdir for that).
Example:
info: Processing /Users/marisa/dev/epub-a11y-checker/samples/build/epub-a11y-tests-001.epub info: Parsing EPUB info: Analyzing accessibility metadata info: Checking package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Http API</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/http-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/http-api/</guid>
      <description>Starting the server After installing Ace, run the ace-http command from the terminal. There are a few options listed below.
Ace by DAISY, an Accessibility Checker for EPUB Usage: ace-http [options] Options: -h, --help output usage information -v, --version output the version number -H, --host set the server&#39;s hostname (default: localhost) -p, --port set the server&#39;s port (default: 8000) -V, --verbose display verbose output -s, --silent do not display any output Examples $ ace-http -p 3000  API This API is available to client applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML Report</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-html/</guid>
      <description>Ace&amp;rsquo;s outputs a human-readable report in HTML format, detailing the automated tests. You can see which tests failed and why; and also see extracted data, such as a list of images, along with accessibility information for each, to highlight potential problem areas and to assist in manual checking.
The header Includes the version of Ace, the report date, and some basic metadata extracted from the book, for identifying the publication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Report</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-json/</guid>
      <description>Ace&amp;rsquo;s outputs a machine-readable report in JSON format, detailing the automated tests. The vocabulary of this report is a mix of EARL (Evaluation and Reporting Language), basic Dublin Core terms, and custom fields.
Document structure Each example chunk of the report shown below appears in order, in one JSON file.
 Header information Outlines Image list Iframes list Properties earl:testSubject for this EPUB file Accessibility metadata summary Assertions  Header information { &amp;quot;@type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;earl:report&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;dct:title&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Ace Report&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;dct:description&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;Report on automated accessibility checks for EPUB&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;dct:date&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;10/8/2017, 1:08:03 PM&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;earl:assertedBy&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;@type&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;earl:software&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;doap:name&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;DAISY Ace&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;doap:description&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;DAISY Accessibility Checker for EPUB&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;doap:homepage&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;http://ace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/config/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ace can be configured through a config.json file located in an OS-specific directory:
 on Windows in &amp;quot;%HOME%\AppData\Local\DAISY Ace\Config\&amp;quot; on macOS in &amp;quot;~/Library/Preferences/DAISY\ Ace/&amp;quot; on Linux in &amp;quot;~/.config/DAISY Ace/&amp;quot;  Defaults The defaults for Ace configuration are:
{ &amp;quot;logging&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;fileName&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;ace.log&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;level&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;info&amp;quot; }, &amp;quot;output&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;force&amp;quot;: false, &amp;quot;subdir&amp;quot;: false } &amp;quot;runtime&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;concurrencyLevel&amp;quot;: 4 } }  Reference logging.fileName Default: &amp;ldquo;info&amp;ldquo;
The name of the file used by Ace to print a log of runtime messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/logging/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ace prints a log of messages in a ace.log file located in an OS-specific directory:
 on Windows in &amp;quot;%HOME%\AppData\Local\DAISY Ace\Log\&amp;quot; on macOS in &amp;quot;~/Library/Logs/DAISY\ Ace/&amp;quot; on Linux in &amp;quot;~/.local/state/DAISY Ace/&amp;quot;  Configuration The logging level and the name of the log file can be configured through Ace’s config file. Read more on Ace configuration to know more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>