<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reference on Ace, by DAISY</title>
    <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reference on Ace, by DAISY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Command line interface</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/cli/</guid>
      <description>Overview The easiest way to run Ace is to type this on the command line:
$ ace ~/Documents/book.epub  You&amp;rsquo;ll then see a description of Ace&amp;rsquo;s actions as it runs tests on the book. The JSON report is printed to the command line at the end (nothing is saved to disk; you need to specify --outdir for that).
Example:
info: Processing ../epub-a11y-checker/samples/build/epub-a11y-tests-001.epub info: Parsing EPUB info: Analyzing accessibility metadata info: Checking package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML Report</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-html/</guid>
      <description>Ace outputs a human-readable report in HTML format, containing information about which automated tests failed, as well as extracted data visualizations, to highlight potential problem areas and to assist in manual checking.
Note that the report looks best with javascript enabled, though it&amp;rsquo;s not required.
After the header, which contains the Ace version, report date, and publication title, there are four sections, detailed below.
Violations Summary of Violations This table lists statistics for the violations, in terms of severity: Critical, Serious, Moderate, or Minor; and by ruleset category: WCAG 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Report</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/report-json/</guid>
      <description>Ace&amp;rsquo;s outputs a machine-readable report in JSON format, detailing the automated tests. The vocabulary of this report is a mix of EARL (Evaluation and Reporting Language), Dublin Core, and custom terms.
Document structure Each example piece of the report shown below appears in order, in one JSON file.
 Header information Outlines Data Properties earl:testSubject for this EPUB file Accessibility metadata summary Assertions  Header information This gives basic information about Ace and when the report was created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/config/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ace can be configured through a config.json file located in an OS-specific directory:
 on Windows in &amp;quot;%HOME%\AppData\Local\DAISY Ace\Config\&amp;quot; on macOS in &amp;quot;~/Library/Preferences/DAISY\ Ace/&amp;quot; on Linux in &amp;quot;~/.config/DAISY Ace/&amp;quot;  Defaults The defaults for Ace configuration are:
{ &amp;quot;cli&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;return-2-on-validation-error&amp;quot;: false }, &amp;quot;logging&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;fileName&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;ace.log&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;level&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;info&amp;quot; }, &amp;quot;output&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;force&amp;quot;: false, &amp;quot;subdir&amp;quot;: false }, &amp;quot;runtime&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;concurrencyLevel&amp;quot;: 4 }, &amp;quot;report&amp;quot;: { &amp;quot;use-relative-paths&amp;quot;: true } }  Reference cli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/logging/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ace prints a log of messages in a ace.log file located in an OS-specific directory:
 on Windows in &amp;quot;%HOME%\AppData\Local\DAISY Ace\Log\&amp;quot; on macOS in &amp;quot;~/Library/Logs/DAISY\ Ace/&amp;quot; on Linux in &amp;quot;~/.local/state/DAISY Ace/&amp;quot;  Configuration The logging level and the name of the log file can be configured through Ace’s config file. Read more on Ace configuration to know more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Http API</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/http-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/docs/http-api/</guid>
      <description>Starting the server After installing Ace, run the ace-http command from the terminal:
$ ace-http info: [ace-http] server listening on http://localhost:8000  The command line options are printed when you run ace-http --help:
Ace by DAISY, an Accessibility Checker for EPUB Usage: ace-http [options] Options: -h, --help output usage information -v, --version output the version number -H, --host set the server&#39;s hostname (default: localhost) -p, --port set the server&#39;s port (default: 8000) -V, --verbose display verbose output -s, --silent do not display any output Examples $ ace-http -p 3000  API This API is available to client applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>