<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rules on Ace, by DAISY</title>
    <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rules on Ace, by DAISY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTML Rules</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/html/</guid>
      <description>Under the hood, most of the accessibility checks ran by Ace are powered by Deque axe, an engine for automated testing of HTML. Ace uses axe&amp;rsquo;s rules, with some modifications (described here).
Rules Here is a list of axe&amp;rsquo;s rules used by Ace (see the full up to date documentation in GitHub ):
   Rule ID Description     accesskeys Ensures every accesskey attribute value is unique   aria-allowed-role Ensures role attribute has an appropriate value for the element   aria-dialog-name Ensures every ARIA dialog and alertdialog node has an accessible name   aria-text Ensures &amp;quot;role=text&amp;quot; is used on elements with no focusable descendants   aria-treeitem-name Ensures every ARIA treeitem node has an accessible name   empty-heading Ensures headings have discernible text   epub-type-has-matching-role Ensure the element has an ARIA role matching its epub:type   frame-tested Ensures &amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;frame&amp;gt; elements contain the axe-core script   frame-title-unique Ensures &amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;frame&amp;gt; elements contain a unique title attribute   heading-order Ensures the order of headings is semantically correct   identical-links-same-purpose Ensure that links with the same accessible name serve a similar purpose   image-redundant-alt Ensure image alternative is not repeated as text   label-title-only Ensures that every form element is not solely labeled using the title or aria-describedby attributes   landmark-banner-is-top-level Ensures the banner landmark is at top level   landmark-complementary-is-top-level Ensures the complementary landmark or aside is at top level   landmark-contentinfo-is-top-level Ensures the contentinfo landmark is at top level   landmark-main-is-top-level Ensures the main landmark is at top level   landmark-no-duplicate-banner Ensures the document has at most one banner landmark   landmark-no-duplicate-contentinfo Ensures the document has at most one contentinfo landmark   landmark-no-duplicate-main Ensures the document has at most one main landmark   landmark-one-main Ensures the document has a unique main landmark   landmark-unique Landmarks should have a unique role or role/label/title (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EPUB Rules</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/epub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/rules/epub/</guid>
      <description>In addition to the HTML rules, Ace has a set of rules that are EPUB-specific:
   Rule Description     epub-pagesource Ensures that if the content has page breaks, the print source is identified in the Package Document metadata with dc:source.   epub-title Ensures that the EPUB’s title is defined in the Package Document.   epub-type-has-matching-role Ensures that the element has an ARIA role matching its epub:type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
