<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributing on Ace, by DAISY</title>
    <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributing on Ace, by DAISY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to contribute?</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/contributing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/contributing/</guid>
      <description>First, welcome to Ace and thank you so much for willing to contribute!
Submitting an issue Feel free to file issues on our GitHub issue tracker.
When filing an issue, please provide the following details:
 the version of Ace impacted by the issue (it can be retrieved by running ace -v in a command shell). the version of Node used to run Ace (it can be retrieved by running node -v in a command shell).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code base overview</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/code/</guid>
      <description>Ace consists of the following components:
 core: the core checker’s logic, and the code responsible for running the underlying Web checker cli: the command line interface epub: utils for parsing EPUBs http: the Http API report: utils for building Ace’s reports scripts: the Javascript files injected in the headless browser to run Ace’s checks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementation notes</title>
      <link>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daisy.github.io/ace/contributing/notes/</guid>
      <description>Design principles TBD.
HTML checker Under the hood, most of the HTML checks are powered by aXe, an engine for automated testing of HTML from Deque Systems.
Headless browser During the evaluation of an EPUB, Ace loads each HTML content documeent in a headless browser using Nightmare.js, a high-level browser automatiom library from Segment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>